go far away. Kobe, you assume you had
other options. Why did you pick the
Bears? And what do you like about the
whole situation here?
>> Uh, I mean, honestly, just feeling
wanted. Um, you know, that's the feeling
I had and you know, God told me, you
know, just to choose his place and
that's what happened. So,
>> you come out highest to highs in in
football. Would you describe as the
experience you had going through that
whole run with Seattle?
>> Definitely. um thankful you know the
opportunity I had in Seattle winning the
Super Bowl and you know just being a
part of that but um you know it came to
an end and now I'm here. So
>> what was what were your sentiments on
what made that defense so special to
play in?
>> Yeah, just playing together uh being on
the same page um having fun know trials
and tribulations but ultimately you know
we just stayed together and uh got the
job done.
>> What do you want to bring to this
defense?
>> Leadership. um you know, taking the ball
away, you know, just being just being
great each and every week. You know, we
can definitely do that. Uh taking it one
game at a time and you know, continue to
perfect greatness.
>> Is there an excitement from you to get
to work without Harris here in Chicago?
>> Yeah, definitely. Definitely. Uh I
couldn't stop smiling honestly. You
know, just the guys that he previously
worked with had seven plus
interceptions. So, I look forward to
that for sure.
>> What can you learn from know what it
takes to to win a Super Bowl to get to
that point? Do you see this Bears team
as an as an ascending team that has some
of those traits?
>> Yeah, absolutely. Big reason why I chose
to be here. Um, got the right guys, the
right coaching staff. You know, just
like I said, just taking it one day at a
time and starting the OTAAS.
>> What did you learn about that Super Bowl
or from what did you learn from the
Super Bowl?
>> Yeah.
>> That you think you can apply to your own
career and apply to your teammates who
haven't?
>> Yeah, just controlling what you can
control and like I said, just taking it
one week at a time. It's a long season.
Um, you know, and like I said, don't get
complacent and, you know, each week just
continues to get better.
>> When you're making conversion to safety,
what were the biggest challenges of that
and what ways you could get brought out?
>> Yeah. Uh, the biggest thing was
communication, the open field tackling.
Um, you know, that's something I can
always, you know, continue to get better
on too. Um, you know, just it was a big
challenge, but, you know, I knew I could
do it and it, you know, it set my career
up to be how it is and continues to get
better. with Dennis Allen, he likes
versatile DBs. Do you imagine that some
of that cornerback skill will probably
be you'll have to lean on some of that
in this scheme, too?
>> Yeah, for sure. Um, I can play football,
honestly. You know, doesn't matter where
it's at, but just I feel like he's
definitely going to help me utilize my,
you know, my tools and go out there and
be the best version of myself. For sure.
>> In a sense, do you feel like you're
still learning how to play safety since
it's only been a couple years?
>> Yes, for sure. Um, it's only been here
two, year two playing safety. Obviously,
I can always get better at all things,
honestly. So just continuously, you
know, improve on whatever it is. So
>> see any parallels between a city like
Seattle where I mean the Seahawks are
huge there where the Bears actually are
probably the most prominent team in
town.
>> Yeah, definitely. Definitely. I would
say it's a lot colder here. Um you know
I'm from Cleveland, so I'm used to that.
But definitely excited to be here. Um
heard tons of great things honestly. A
lot closer to home, my family. So very
excited. What's the day been like just
kind of being in a good place of going
to the first time and going through that
>> crazy I'm off of like three hours of
sleep. So I can't wait to go back to
sleep honestly on on the plane you know
but like I said I'm excited. Like I said
I feel loved here honestly. Great group
of guys over there too as well too. So
I'm excited.
>> Last season looked like one of your most
explosive. You didn't have a lot of
wasted movement
>> and it felt it seemed like you were very
comfortable at the safety position. What
do you think you can add coming into
this season to get even better? even
more. Honestly, I'm just scratching the
surface. Like I said, it's only year two
playing safety. Still young. Uh turned
27 in two weeks. So, I would say that's
still young. But, um definitely, you
know, just I'm excited to be here, like
I said, and I feel like the coaching
staff is definitely going to prepare me
to be not just a better player, but a
better leader for the room and for the
team as well, too. So, I'm excited.
>> Is it hard to leave a place that you
just won a Super Bowl with? Yeah,
obviously, um, you know, just the
relationship that I built with, you
know, my teammates over there and the
coaches staff, but like I said, um, I
feel like I was chosen to be here and,
you know, I'm excited to be here with
with those guys. So,
>> Kobe, you came you came very close, uh,
last playoffs to play in the Bears
instead of the Rams. What' you think of
that game and what' you think of that
Bears team?
>> Yeah, I was definitely watching it. I
was actually telling, you know, a couple
guys and even my family, I honestly
thought we were going to play the the
Bears in NFC Championship, but it didn't
work out like that. But um that's like I
said, it was a big reason why I came
here. I seen the the winning culture,
the head coach, and just the coaching
staff. I knew, you know, high
expectations for sure.
>> You're on the other side of the ball.
But what role does Caleb Williams play
in you finding this an attractive place
to come?
>> Yeah. Um I actually had to play him two
years ago. So, uh you know, I I seen,
you know, how special he was from day
one. He actually reached out to me um
when I did sign and I felt like that's,
you know, special, you know, the
quarterback reaching out to a safety. Um
you know, even though in practice, I'm
definitely going to try to get on him
for sure. So, but um definitely, you
know, just him reaching out says a lot
honestly and I'm looking forward to
playing against him.
>> What do you think when he threw that
touchdown against the Rams? Run it
backwards.
>> That was elite, honestly. You know, you
can't coach things like that. You know,
that's just who he is. Um like he's even
just scratching the surface. Year three.
Um high expectations and I expect, you
know, greatness from him for sure.
>> We have a couple of times. What's your
leadership style of your lead by
example? Last person on the field kind
of guy or you more vocal in the room?
>> Could be all three, honestly. Um, you
know, but right now I feel like I'm
going to lead by example, you know, just
cuz I'm on a new team. But, you know, I
I'll show show by that and eventually be
more vocal and, you know, I'm always
going to stay after on the on the
practice field or whatever the case may
be. So,
>> you said what was the pray like?
>> Pray like. Yeah, it was like
>> can't really describe it cuz um I'm not
going to say too much, but uh
>> yeah, just know I had a great time.
Sure.
>> Awesome. Thanks, coach. Yeah. Thank you.
>> When did you first find out the Bears
were interested in and how did you
process?
>> Uh I first found out uh what was it? Uh
noon when the negotiation started. Bears
came on pretty strong and that's kind of
when everything kind of took off.
>> How do you make that determination so
quick? Do you do some research? Uh did
you do one of those zooms that you can
do now with them or?
>> No, I didn't do a Zoom. It was all
through uh my agent. Um and uh basically
uh it was just a discussion of uh offers
and what they were offering and what
they wanted me to be.
>> As you get here today, what's your
understanding of kind of how you will
fit within within the plans defensively?
>> Yeah. Um obviously uh my play style um
and uh they're looking for a guy with my
play style to come in and fit in DA's
system.
>> Reflect on the season you had last year.
What what really clicked for you last
season?
>> Um man, I was just playing football. um
doing what I always been doing. Um
nothing really changed. I didn't change
anything in the offseason. I didn't
change anything during the season. Um I
kind of just stuck to my routine and uh
went out there and executed.
>> After your injury, how long do you think
it took you to maybe regain your speed?
>> Um probably took about a probably a good
year.
>> Having gone through that and dealt with
like expectations and injuries and all
those battled through that, what kind of
a player are the Bears getting in you
now? What did you learn from that?
>> Yeah. Um, man, my my experience probably
is probably a big thing. Um, if if they
didn't already talk about that. Um, you
know, I'm going into year eight. Uh, I
came into this league at 20 years old,
so you can kind of say I grew up in this
league. So, I mean, there's nothing I
haven't seen. Uh, practice against Big
Ben for three years. Um, played against
Aaron Rogers twice a year for two years.
Um, so played against Philip Rivers. So,
I mean, I I didn't I didn't seen a lot
of things. Um, been through a lot of
different situations. So, I think I
bring that type of experience to this
team.
>> What do you remember from the game you
played at Soldier Field? Outside of the
fact it was really really cool.
>> Uh, it was it was nice. Uh, it was my
first time actually playing in Chicago.
Uh, so it was my first time experience.
It was it was super cold. Um, stating
was beautiful and uh the fans was
outstanding. The atmosphere was really
good. So, uh, it was a good impression
for me. Is is last year the type of
season you kind of envisioned yourself
having when you first came into the
league as a
>> uh I mean that's my expectation every
year um since little league is to go out
there and and make as much plays as I
could. Um you know the plays come and
you got to make them. So I mean I didn't
predict that it was going to happen like
that but I was ready for the
opportunity.
>> So what's a week like this like? You
know you wake up Monday not knowing
where you're going to be playing and by
Thursday you're you're standing in a new
organization figure it all out.
>> It's fast but I mean that's what this
league is. I mean, guys come in every
year, guys retire every year, and uh you
know, rosters change every year. So, I
mean, it's it's just what it is.
>> What's your initial impression of of
what you're joining here?
>> Uh it's nice. Uh I like the facility. Uh
everybody that I met so far is very
welcoming. Um support seems looks like
it's very great here. Uh they have a
really good team, uh young team at that
and uh they're looking to add some
pieces to go to the next level.
>> Are you familiar with the the history of
linebackers team? Yes.
>> What kind of stands out to you? Any
linebackers come to mind right away?
>> Um, of course, Brian Erlacer. Um, was it
Mike Singleary? Uh, should I even throw
Roan Smith out there? I remember I
follow his game since Georgia Bulldogs.
So, I mean, those type of guys. Yeah.
But, uh, I feel like, um, you know, they
brought me here. I'm a different type of
linebacker. You know, I'm not the 6'2,
250 kind of guy, you know, I'm the 5'11,
you know, 225 type of guy. So, uh, it's
obviously going to be a little
different, but, uh, you know, I plan on,
uh, holding a high standard to myself
and, you know, hopefully making those
guys, uh, proud.
>> Last year, do you feel like they made a
schematic change, uh, that helped you
click? And was there a particular coach
that had the the greatest impact on you
in that?
>> Yeah, my position coach, uh, Jason Tar,
he's been in the league uh, for a while.
Um, probably the best coach I had in the
league um, so far. Uh, really smart guy,
football guy. Um, all he does is
football and that's my type of people
because that's I don't got no hobbies.
All I do is football. So,
>> you got a dose of of the playoffs and
competing for that early on in your
career. What does it mean to come to a
team that's coming off a division title
and with larger aspirations moving
forward?
>> Uh, I want to be a part of it. Uh, big
reason why I signed here. So, um, you
know, I'm coming in ready to work. Um,
you know, there's there's not going to
be no drop off. There's not going to be
no adjustment period. I'm coming here.
I'm year eight. I'm be expected to come
in, learn the playbook, and and produce.
>> Deon, what do you remember about that
pick six you had against Joe Burrow last
season?
>> Uh, man, it was a long run, about
another seven yards. Uh, it was it was a
highlight of of the season for for me
for real, just because, uh, you know,
linebackers usually don't score as much
as I did last year. But, uh, it was
good, man. I I appreciated every moment
I had last year.
>> Ryan Paul, talk about
>> adding speed to this defense. I mean,
how much pride do you take in being one
of Have you always been fast? Like,
>> yeah.
>> Yeah, that's my strength. Uh, that's
that's my play style. Um, that's just
how I always been. So, I mean, it ain't
nothing new for me. Like I said, I got
to come in here and produce.
>> Thank you.
>> Know your faces here with Ben and and L.
What was it like to come in here and
know that you were going to be reuniting
with both?
>> Um, man, really, really nice. Um, I've
been on a couple new teams before, so
uh, I always tell people to that first
year going to another team, man, no
matter if you're young or old, to be
able to have that adjustment period is a
real thing. Um, but the more familiarity
you have, whether it be faces, scheme,
all the other things, man, it helps kind
of reduce that time it takes to get
adjusted. So, um, having a familiar face
uh, with L, with BJ, um, knowing HTC,
how he works, man, uh, hoping to cut
that time down, man, so we get the the
work ethic part of it through the door.
So, yes, sir. When did you know that Ben
would be a head coach?
>> Um,
the time that I knew who Ben was, he had
this picture. Uh, literally, I bring it
up all the time. Um, he talks about his
time at he was he was in Miami. Um, just
went through a transition, whatever.
He's like, "It's a picture of the beach.
You think I'd be really, really happy,
but it's one of the hardest times of my
life." Um but to understand that kind of
guy to go through something like that
and then to watch his work ethic in the
building um that's when you know
somebody has something in them that's uh
either a little different whether it's
competitive competitive spirit whether
it's a will whatever it is that's when
you know somebody has something like
that in them and when somebody has that
it doesn't matter what role they're
going to take it's going to be uh
they're going to do very well for
themselves. So
>> So he has a picture of the beach.
>> Yeah. It was like I think it was a
picture he posted a while he he just he
brought up to the group one day. He's
like, man, this is a, you know, it's a
picture of my I'm on the beach,
everything, but uh I'm just going
through a coaching transition right now.
So, you think I'd be happy, but my mind
is what I have in front of me, what I
have to achieve, and um you take got
that kind of guy with that kind of work
ethic who you can't get to sleep because
he's doing so much work. Um that's when
you know he's got it, man. So, you got a
guy that'll work like that and who's
been through something like that, that's
kind of guy you'll follow anywhere. So,
>> what did you make of good, better, best?
Watching that from afar and seeing him
take his shirt off after the Eagles
game.
>> No, man. That's that's uh that's who he
is, man. I never forget the first day he
uh he had everybody saying and
everybody, you know, it's good, better,
best. You know, you know, you're not
used to doing like chance stuff like
that and then we started winning and
then he started doing it here and then
everybody's winning. So, I'm like, well,
we better be good, better, best then.
So, uh no, it's uh it's it's a testament
to who he is, man. He's not taking shirt
off cuz he wants the looks, man. He's
taking a shut off probably cuz he
probably slept three hours that week and
they to go put all the work in to go win
the game. So, um it's a testament to who
he is and um No, I'm proud of him.
>> What do you think of this receiver core
here that the Bears have?
>> Yeah, I think it's a bunch of talent,
man. Um we always uh back in my previous
team, man, we always talk about, you
know, just receiving cores, how people
line up coming out the draft. Um J Mo's
always talking about Luther like, man,
no, he's where I'm from. That's my boy.
He's nice. and um a lot of talent on the
field, man. Um I think one of the
sentiments Ryan gave to Luther, every
time he touched the ball, man, he can go
the distance. Um he's just explosive guy
playing against him, watching him on
film. Um you see that on tape. Same
thing with Romeo, man. It's just it's a
you guys know hard time, man, but just
um a lot of a lot of talent on the
field, man. So, um hopefully the work
that we put in uh over the course of the
next few months shows up in September.
So
>> you had some adversity early in your
career before you kind of connected with
Detroit. What was the difference there?
Did it just click like at one point?
What do you look back at as the moment
where you just kind of established
yourself with the Lions?
>> Um, a little bit of all thing, man.
There's a there's I will say every time
that I got I've been cut a lot of times.
Um, but each time I always tell myself
I'm not going to get cut from the same
thing twice. Um, and thankfully uh by
the grace of God I had more than one
opportunity to be able to learn from.
And eventually, man, if you work hard
enough, uh, you'll be able to round out
your game. And then the NFL, man, as you
guys know, it's a it's a 1% game, man.
It's very, very slim pickings out here.
So, you kind of have to have that work
ethic, some talent, but you also kind of
need a little bit of luck, man. And, uh,
I ran into a very, very positive
situation over there. Um, it gave me an
opportunity to be able to show what I
can do. And, uh, so I'm forever grateful
for that. But, it gave me the
opportunity to grow. So, that way 2021,
I first get there, I was a better player
in 2022. And I'm just constantly been
working on my game. Um, but it g they
gave me the opportunity there. So, I'm
very thankful for it.
>> Would you say it's mental? I read about
you doing meditation and stuff like
that.
>> Oh yeah. Um, this game's like 90%
mental. Um, and I would even go I mean,
you can almost go 95 cuz I always tell
everybody when they come to Lee. I'm
like, dude, everybody runs a 4-3.
Apparently, don't matter if you're
outside linebacker or if you're a
receiver, don't matter. Everybody runs a
4-3. Everybody's big, everybody's
strong, everybody's fast. Um, but if the
mental side of it, handling the
pressure, um, knowing what to do. I was,
uh, I was at a camp and I said, "Oh, you
guys all like Odell, right?" And I was
like, "Yeah, Odell get the one-handed
catch, right?" Well, if Odell runs a
curl and a quarterback threw a post, can
Odell run a one-handed catch? And like,
you're like, "Well, no." And I'm like,
"Just that." I mean, it's so much mental
part of this game between knowing the
playbook, um, handling the pressure, um,
even studying the extra 30 minutes to an
hour a day, all that stuff adds up. So
being able to handle that, control your
emotions, um to not be high and low, to
kind of stay even kill, um to be able to
handle that pressure, man, it's it's a
big deal. So um yeah, definitely 90%
that's what separates the average player
who has sparks of talent versus the guy
who ends up being great and constantly
um improves. So Yes, sir.
>> How do you describe your your style as a
returner, punt returner specifically?
>> Um how would I how would I describe my
style? Um, I you know I you you could
say aggressive. Um, but I always say I'm
only I'm aggressive because I trust the
guys in front of me and I trust the work
we put in because we we we do a lot of
work during the week between catching
the punts, doing a rep. So, um,
eventually like I look at I'm like,
"Hey, look, I'm I trust you." Like the
decision made like when you give me that
look in my eye, I'm like, I'm not even
going to look down to see if there's a
posit. I'm I'm taking this cuz I trust
you guys. You develop that rapport after
a while. But uh a lot of it also has to
do over the last five years I've had a
chance to kind of learn the game, learn
the statistics. Um even like for
instance like the plus 50 punts. I just
got talking to HTT about it. Um you
talked to a lot of the offensive
coordinators. They're like hey look it's
only two or three yards but the playbook
is opens up between 8 yard line and 11
or the 13 yard line. Like I remember
others one I think I got to the 20 on
one of them like man we just our whole
play call just changed. So having that
understanding um on the field,
tendencies and things like that. Um if
you can be aggressive, it's better. Um
football always used to say, man, you
don't know if the ball's going to bounce
your way. Um so being able to catch it,
trying to get on everything, but
trusting our guys and trying to find the
hidden yardage because there's so many
points and percentages within the hidden
yardage. So um I feel like the ball's in
our hands, if we put the work in, the
percentage is always going to be better
if we can be aggressive. But
>> uh Khif, what do you come in knowing
about Richard High Totower and the
emphasis uh that the Bears put on
special teams in particular?
>> Oh, I mean they put it this way, they've
always had some guys both back there in
the return game, but also in their core
unit. Um and I feel like what you see on
film um from their unit, from our unit
is a is a testament to the work they put
in, but also the details that the coach
the coach implements. So they were
always a very very impressive unit. And
even from a return standpoint, I mean,
no matter who was back there, you kind
of always held your breath cuz there was
always a possibility on tape like, hey
man, they were this close to breaking
one here and there. So when you got guys
that pop like that on the unit, um it's
a testament to the work put in and the
details for the a lot of the little
stuff, man. So um a lot of respect
coming from HT um for myself. Um so I'm
excited to work with them.
>> You expect to do more kick returning?
>> Um I'm expected to do whatever they
asked me to and that's kind of been my
role for the last few years. Um, the
good thing about the last couple years
is I've been able to kind of round out
my game, do a lot of work behind the
scenes, uh, to prepare, um, for a really
good opportunity. So, um, I've always
molded myself to wherever the team needs
me. That's kind of how I've been here
for so long, but, uh, I'm prepared to do
that and I've been able to do that the
last few years. So, um, whatever they
need me to do, I'll be ready to do.
>> Khalif, outside of the familiar faces,
what else was explained to you during
this process that made you feel like the
Bears are the right fit for me right
now? Um to be honest, uh a lot of the a
lot of the history um watch I was just
telling somebody I can't replicate half
the stuff he does, but a lot of Devon
Hester stuff. Um but there's there's
there's so much history in this
building. As soon as you walk in, man,
it's like, okay, man, if this on a tail
end of my career, you know what I'm
saying? Later in my years, man, to be
able to play for organization like this
with this kind of people um that has
this kind of resounding positivity
coming throughout the league of being
able to play here. Um it's it's a great
opportunity for me. Um, my wife is was
born in uh, Chicago, so it's almost like
coming back home for my first NFL game
uh, was versus the Bears. So, it was
just so much history here, man. It was
the right time. We just had a
fourmonth-old. Uh, so like now we can
actually like uproot and go a little
bit. So, we just had a baby. She's four
months now, but it was the right time
uh, for us. And, uh, I'm very excited to
be here. So, you're
>> a history guy. Is that why you picked
the the Staleies hat?
>> So, okay. So, there's two things. One,
>> I'm not that I'm not that cool. Um, I
wish. Um, so I walked in with the White
Socks hat and I'm like looking at the
right and I just see like eyes just like
like what are you doing? And then
Antoine Ren L is like you got to take it
off. I'm like I'm like what's up? How
you doing man? He's like take the hat
off. I'm like oh okay. Um so apparently
you got to pick one side or the other.
So I like look is anybody got any other
hat out here because I need a little bit
of help. And they brought this one out.
So um I'm about to go apparently this is
a it's a big time hat. So I'm about to
go do a bunch of research right now to
uh get this right. But no. Yeah.
Thank you.
>> What led you to the Bears this
opportunity? What do you see for
yourself in this organization?
>> Just, you know, just kind of as the
process started, um, you know, when it
was time to make that decision, I
thought it was a great opportunity to be
a part of something special. Um, when I
got the call when free agency started, I
thought it was a it was a great
opportunity. You know, just the history
of, you know, the culture here,
especially when it comes to defense and
the standard that is that's here. Um,
you know, I wanted to be a part of I
wanted to be a part of something
special. I wanted to have an opportunity
to take my game to another level and I
thought this would be a great fit for
what we're trying to build here
defensively.
>> You obviously experienced at changing
teams over the last several years. What
have you learned about the the
transition process that helps you kind
of get acclimated quicker?
>> I think the the biggest thing for me is
like you know like I've told any player,
you got to love it. You know, I love the
process. I love the opportunity. Just,
you know, I don't take this for granted.
Obviously, you know, being a being a
part of different teams, you know, it's
bittersweet. And I say bitter because,
you know, the transition from one to
another and, you know, when you build a
relationship with certain guys and you
grind with certain guys, you know, it it
hurts a little bit, but then you get an
opportunity to grow. It it causes you to
demand more of yourself from a mental
standpoint, you know, being able to
still be effective, apply your knowledge
into different systems while still
trying to build something special with
the guys. So, I feel like that's allowed
me to continue to prove and kind of
reestablish that love, you know, uh that
you got to have, you know, when it comes
to the process.
>> How do you describe what makes you
effective as a run stopper?
>> Just, uh, being able to be effective
all, you know, throughout any position
on the defensive line. Um, I think my my
effort and my desire to compete at a
high level, um, I think it speaks
volumes. That's something that I take
pride in. That's something that I've
always tried to if apart from obviously
being effective as a D lineman I think
you know the effort and desire to you
know to be at 100% and not take plays
off. I think that's something that I
take pride in that's it's carried it's
carried me up to this point has been a
part of my journey and I think being
here is is great for that.
>> This might be a dumb question but how
did you get into football as a kid?
>> What do I mean?
>> How did you get into football as a kid?
>> How did I get into football as a kid?
>> Yeah. Um, you know, obviously for those
you don't know, I was born and raised in
Canada. So, obviously, you know, the the
football it's it's good football out
there. Obviously, night and day, you
know, when you cross the border, but,
you know, I just always uh been in love
with the game. I I actually, you know,
little fun fact,
kind of, you know, guess I was back and
forth with this size, but my favorite
player at the time was a
was David Gard. Thought I was going to
be a quarterback. Couldn't really move
ball like that, you know. I I I told
myself, you know, you know, I was going
to find my myself in the league in one
day. Just happened to be, you know,
three tech, nose tack, and all that. But
yeah, game has always been a part of me.
You know, again, we we watch a lot of
football where I'm at. And then, you
know, for me, the biggest thing was I
wanted to see how far I could take my
game. And no better place to take it
than going across the border and playing
ball.
>> Nobody tried to Nobody tried to make you
a defenseman in hockey or anything like
that.
I wasn't the best skater,
>> you know, but if I could skate well, I
probably had that in the back of my bag,
too. You
>> playing quarterback growing up.
>> See, that's the thing that that arm,
that arm wasn't cutting it.
I watched David Gard, you know, he was
on a, you know, dominant player, you
know, definitely one of the bigger
quarterbacks could run. So, I thought,
hey, man, like that could have been me.
I could run that arm, though. That arm
wasn't where it needed to be. So I'm
like, I'm going just stay on the line.
>> Neville, the the speed definitely
translate in your game. How does that
help you as a defensive player?
>> I I think it, you know, being a being a
D lineman that it's it's only it's
always a great thing, right? Because the
thing I take pride in is obviously, you
know, you got to be effective as D
lineman, you got to be able to stop the
run. You got to be able to affect the
quarterback. But I think for me, you
know, I think the best way to show that
you care, that you love the game is
through your effort. And obviously I've
been I've been blessed to have the
speed, but I feel like I try my best to
take advantage of that. So, you know,
I'm the kind of guy, don't necessarily
speak on it, but you know, it's evident
I I want to make sure I try to be around
the ball as much as possible. And I feel
like the way to show your team, show
your defense, show the guys you care, is
when you're a big dude that can, you
know, do his job in the front, but is a
guy that's going to run 20, 30 yards
down the field, whatever it may be, to
to make plays. And that's how I take I
take pride in doing that.
What excites you about being in Dennis
Allen's system here at Chicago?
>> Very exciting. You know, you you just
see like, you know, when you look at his
history, you see the guys that he's
worked with in the past, even back when
New Orleans, and then, you know, what
they're establishing here, you know, you
got, you know, young guy like Dexter,
you got a guy like Grady Jared being
here, the guys that they brought along,
and I I feel like a guy myself, you
know, that has the, you know, the love
for the game and the desire to compete
and fly around, I feel like it goes hand
in hand. So just the opportunity to be a
part of this this system is great. You
know, I'm looking forward to opportunity
not only to get better, but to dominate
with the guys that we have in this room
and and I feel like, you know, again
with the speed, guys who love football,
guys want to make plays, guys who want
to take it another step further than
last year. I think this is a great
opportunity for myself.
>> I'm curious how David Gerrard gets that
much on your radar.
>> Man, I I don't want I don't know. I
think it was just a quiz. Like again, I
even though I was always big for my age,
you know, I felt I always like to say I
was like a skilled player trapped in the
Dline's body. And then, you know, just
see him do certain thing. I don't know.
I just happen to watch TV. He popped up.
I'm like, man, it doesn't look like the
time. He didn't look like your, you
know, your your typical quarterback. And
then, you know, like he could run. He
can do some things. I could run. Just
again, he had that arm. And, you know,
again, at quarterback, that level of
expertise that wasn't my my specialty.
So, I let him have it. But, yeah, it
just so happens that
>> will you lobby your new creative head
coach to maybe try to use you as some
>> I mean, you know, sometimes you got to
look yourself in the mirror
face reality. So, you know, we're trying
to win games. You know, we're not going
to play around with that, but you know,
in another life, in a past life,
probably.